Guide to the Press of the Woolly Whale Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Production Files, 1928-1942; Series III; 7.72; (23 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
  - 99. Gutenberg and the Strasbourg Documents of 1439; prospectus, 1940 (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 200)
  - 105. Take Heed, America, by G. H. Archambault, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - 106. Techniques for Dealing with Artists, by W. A. Dwiggins, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 202-203)
  - 107. This House of Havoc, by Carl Purington Rollins, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 204)
  - 108. A Greeting to Frederick W. Goudy from All the Typophiles, by Paul Standard, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - 109. The Fortsas Bibliohoax, by Walter Klinefelter, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 206-208)
  - 109. The Fortsas Bibliohoax, by Walter Klinefelter, 1942 (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 209)
  - 111. The Oldest Stencil Known, undated (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - 113. Restauration, undated (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - 113. Restauration, undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 212)
  - 114. The Press of the Woolly Whale Presents its Woolly Compliments, undated (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - 114. The Press of the Woolly Whale Presents its Woolly Compliments, undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 214)
  - 117. American Institute of Graphic Arts letterhead, undated (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - 119. Books and Banquet = Institute Book Auction, undated (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - 121. For the Purposes of its Forthcoming Exhibition of Private Press Books of Members, 1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - 123. You are Invited to Attend an Intimate Tasting, undated (Box 24, Folder 218)
  - 126. Ex Libris. Mary Flagler Cary, undated (Box 24, Folder 219)
  - 136. Its friends may now find The Press of the Woolly Whale ..., undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 220)
  - Cary personal projects, undated (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Press of the Woolly Whale projects, undated (Box 24, Folder 222)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts 1939-1940 membership list (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts 1939-1940 membership list (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 224)
  - Euthanasia Society ephemera, undated (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - National Orchestral Association projects, 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - National Orchestral Association projects, undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 227)
  - National Orchestral Association, press sheets for So Practical a Contribution, 1940 (Box 54 (Broadside oversize), Folder 228)
  - "Hunk-a-tin": proposed publication containing a poem about World War I ambulances, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - "Proposed book on the Armistice", 1938 (Box 25, Folder 230-231)
  - Alban Butler drawings (project unidentified), undated (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - Alban Butler drawings (project unidentified), undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 233)
  - Unidentified artwork and printed material, undated (Box 25, Folder 234)
    Includes a drawings for a Typophiles logo featuring Paul Bennett
  - Unidentified artwork and printed material, undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 235)
  - Desk calendar for Melbert B. Cary Sr., 1932 (Box 26, Folder 236-237)
- Press of the Woolly Whale Publications, 1928-1942; Series IV; 9.17; (24 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 58: Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  Series IV is arranged chronologically.
  The series primarily contains publications, both volumes and ephemera, that were produced at the Press of the Woolly Whale. Most of the volumes were labeled "Press Copy," though also kept here are copies created with special papers, inks, coloring, or variant bindings, and some with slipcases or bespoke containers. Exemplars, among others are: (57) The Ninth Man, hand-colored by Fritz Kredel; (96) Gutenberg and the Strasbourg Documents of 1439, bound by Gerhard Gerlach; (98) The Missing Gutenberg Wooden Blocks, bound by Peter Franck; (16) And It Came to Pass, a small Christmas greeting bound by Otto Fratzscher; and (37) Some Thoughts on the Ornamented Mss. of the Middle Ages, by William Morris, for which there are copies bound by six different binders. One copy of (28) Stille Nacht, Heilige Nacht: A Christmas Song is annoted "This is the only copy composed of untreated sheets. All others have been dipped in coffee after printing." There are also are special association copies signed by the authors or others, including (21) The Sentimental Bloke, by C. J. Dennis, which was inscribed by Cary using his family nickname: "for Mary -- to whom the original Sentimental Bloke was sent way back in 1922. Mike."
  The publications are arranged by the checklist number established in David Pankow's annotated bibliography Melbert B. Cary, Jr. and the Press of the Woolly Whale (2002), which is arranged chronologically; numbers in brackets indicate the items that do not appear in the bibliography. Copies of ephemeral items can also be found in Series II, Scrapbooks. Filed at the end of the series is work accomplished for organizations with which the Carys were closely involved; after Cary became president of the American Institute of Graphic Arts (AIGA) the press printed several ephemeral publications for the group.
  The copies of publications in this series are not recorded in Orbis, the library's online catalog.
  - 1. Le Chapeau Immortel, by Earl H. Emmons (broadside), 1928 (Box 52 (Oversize), Folder 238)
  - 2. Ici Vaincu (broadside), 1928 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 239)
    First Armistice Day issue
  - 4. The Vision of Sir Launfal, by James Russell Lowell, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 240-241)
    First Christmas book
  - 5. War, by Richard Le Gallienne, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 242-243)
    Second Armistice Day issue
  - [5a.] Companionship of Stars, by Julia Metcalf Cary, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 244)
  - 6. Behind the Scenes at WEAF on the Occasion of a Concert by Walter Damrosch, January 30, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 245)
  - [6a.] Luncheon in Honor of Franz Helmberger (menu), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 246)
  - 7. Farewell Luncheon in Honor of Karl Hermann Klingspor (menu), 1930 (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - 8. The Press of the Woolly Whale. Anyone who is fortunate... Christmas card, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - 9. A Christmas Carol in Prose: Being a Ghost Story of Christmas, by Charles Dickens, 1930 (Box 31 (Oversize), Folder 249-251)
    Second Christmas book; three copies here: numbers 14, 109, and 140
  - 10. Mademoiselle from Armentieres; illustrated by Alban Butler Jr., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 252-253)
    Third Armistice Day issue
  - 11. Help! Request for Missing Verses of Mademoiselle from Armentieres, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 254)
  - 13. Thou hast most traitorously corrupted... (broadside), 1930 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 255)
    Insert printed for The American Printer (March 1930)
  - 14. Julia M. Cary, 1856-1930, by John Haynes Holmes, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 256-259)
  - 15. Molly Make-Believe, by Eleanor Hallowell, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 260)
    Third Christmas book
  - 15. Molly Make-Believe, by Eleanor Hallowell, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 261)
  - 16. And It Came to Pass [St. Luke, chapter 2] (Christmas greeting), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 262-263)
  - 17. Knowledge and Faith, by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe (broadside), 1932 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 264)
  - 18. Terms of the Armistice, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 265)
    Fourth Armistice Day issue
  - 19. Poverty and Plenty, by Walter Lippmann, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 266)
  - 20. The Scholar in a Troubled World, by Walter Lippmann, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 267)
  - 21. The Sentimental Bloke, by C. J. Dennis, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 268-269)
    Fourth Christmas book
  - 22. A Modern Version of the Night Before Christmas, by Robert McBlair, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 270)
  - 23. Specimen Pages Reprinted from Some of the Books Made at the Press of the Woolly Whale, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 271)
    Insert printed for the Philobiblon (May 1932)
  - 24. The Story of the Village Type, by Frederic W Goudy, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 272-273)
  - 25. Digressions for the Traveller in England, by Melbert B. Cary Jr.; decorations by Warren Chappell, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 274)
  - 26. Patriotism versus Welfare: An Extract from "The Unseen Assassins," by Norman Angell, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 275-276)
    Fifth Armistice Day issue
  - 27. Devil's Bible (26th Yankee Division playing cards); designed by Alban Butler Jr., 1933 (Box 35, Folder 277)
    Sixth Armistice Day issue
  - 28. Stille Nacht, Heilige Nacht: A Christmas Song, by Franz Gruber, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 278-279)
    Fifth Christmas book
  - 29. The Palingenesis of Craps, by Edward Larocque Tinker, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 280)
  - 30. Bank Holiday Luncheon. Stowaways, March 8, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 281)
  - 31. Meine amerikanische Reise (keepsake for luncheon in honor of Aloys Ruppel), 1933 (Box 36, Folder 282)
  - 32. Quinquennalia, 1928-1933; Fifth Birthday Party, Woolly Whale; title page and colophon drawings by Willi Harwerth (Box 36, Folder 283)
  - 33. Five Years, Woolly Whale (invitation), 1933 (Box 36, Folder 284)
  - 34. The Bastard King of England, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 285)
  - 35. 25 Yrs.; A Dinner will be held...to celebrate...the founding of the Stowaways, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 286)
  - 36. Mr. and Mrs. Melbert B. Cary, Jr. request the pleasure... (invitation), [1933 or 1939] (Box 36, Folder 287)
  - 37. Some Thoughts on the Ornamented Mss. of the Middle Ages, by William Morris, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 288-291)
    Issued on the hundreth anniversary of Morris's birth and printed on the Kelmscott/Goudy Press (Albion No. 6551).
    Copies bound by Katharine Adams, E. C. Lewis Company, Douglas Cockerell & Son, and Peter Franck
  - 37. Some Thoughts on the Ornamented Mss. of the Middle Ages, by William Morris, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 292-293)
    Copies bound by Otto Fratzscher and Gerhard Gerlach
  - 38. Design and Beauty in Printing, by Frederic W. Goudy, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 294)
  - 39. Ars Typographica 1, no. 4; edited by Frederic W. Goudy, 1934 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 295-296)
  - 40. An Extract from The Enemies of Books, by William Blades, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 297)
    Sixth Christmas book
  - 41. Mademoiselle from Armentieres, volume two; illustrated by Alban B. Butler Jr., 1934 (Box 37, Folder 298-299)
    Seventh Armistice Day issue
  - 42. Warmest Greetings to Dr. Walter Damrosch... (birthday greeting), 1934 (Box 38, Folder 300)
  - 43. Mademoiselle from Armentieres (prospectus), 1934 (Box 38, Folder 301)
  - 45. Ars Typographica (prospectus), 1934 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 302)
  - 47. The Estivation of Two Mao Tzu, by Melbert B. Cary Jr.; bound by Gerhard Gerlach, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 303-304)
    Seventh Christmas book
  - 47. The Estivation of Two Mao Tzu, by Melbert B. Cary Jr.; bound by Gerhard Gerlach, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 305-308)
  - 48. The Early Art Training of B. R. at Purdue University, by Ernest Knaufft, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 309)
  - 49. Sir Frederic, flask in hand..., 1935 (Box 40, Folder 310)
    Signature printed for Spinach from Many Gardens; Gathered by The Typophiles and Fed to Frederic W. Goudy on his Seventieth Anniversary, 1935
  - 50. Patriotism vs Science, by Gaston Paris, 1935 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 311)
    Ninth Armistice Day issue
  - 52. Jonah and the Woolly Whale Were Breakfasting, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 312)
  - 53. Merry Christmas from Two Mao Tzu (card), 1935 (Box 40, Folder 313)
  - 54. Exaggerated Nationalism, by Richard Le Gallienne, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 314-315)
    Eighth Armistice Day issue
  - 55. Some New Light on the Genesis of the Ampersand, by Melbert B. Cary Jr., 1936 (Box 40, Folder 316)
  - 56. To the Yearly Meeting; Extract Taken from the Minnits of our Quarterly Meeting...1779, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 317)
  - 57. The Ninth Man, by Mary Heaton Vorse; illustrated by Alban B. Butler Jr., 1936 (Box 40, Folder 318-319)
    Eighth Christmas book
  - 57. The Ninth Man, by Mary Heaton Vorse; illustrated by Alban B. Butler Jr., 1936 (Box 41, Folder 320)
  - 58. The Treasure in the Forest, by H. G. Wells, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 321-322)
    With illustrations in stenciled color drawn, cut, and applied by W. A. Dwiggins.
  - 59. Announcing a Typographic Divertissement by Mwano Masassi; The Treasure in the Forest, H.G. Wells, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 323)
  - 60. Americanism: What Is It?; text by Americanism Committee, New York County American Legion, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 324)
  - 61. William Henry Metcalf: A Biography by his Daughter, by Julia Metcalf Cary, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 325-326)
  - 61. William Henry Metcalf: A Biography by his Daughter, by Julia Metcalf Cary, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 327)
  - 62. The First Days of the Village Press: Extracts from the Diary of Will Ransom, MCMIII, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 328)
  - 63. War Cards: A Prolusion, by Melbert B. Cary Jr., 1937 (Box 42, Folder 329-330)
    Tenth Armistice Day issue
  - 64. Index to War Cards, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 331)
  - 65. Announcement (for War Cards ), 1937 (Box 42, Folder 332)
  - 66. Gabrilowitsch Memorial Concert (broadside announcement), 1937 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 333)
  - 67. May Meeting, 1937, The Club of Odd Volumes (announcement) (Box 42, Folder 334)
  - 68. The Press of the Woolly Whale (broadside), 1937 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 335)
  - 69. Excerpts from the Work of The Press of the Woolly Whale, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 336)
  - 70. Devices from [& by] Many Typophiles, by Paul Bennett, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 337)
  - 71. Greetings, by Paul Bennett, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 338)
    Insert printed for Typophiles Keepsake No. 4
  - [71a.] Birthday Greetings WAD from the Typophiles, April 2, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 339)
  - 72. A Bibliography of the Village Press, 1903-1938, by Melbert B. Cary Jr. (Box 43, Folder 340-342)
  - 73. A Prayer for a Wedding, by John Haynes Holmes, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 343-344)
  - 74. Schnitzelbank; Metamorphosed from the Original German with Sketches by Fritz Kredel, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 345-348)
  - 74. Schnitzelbank; Metamorphosed from the Original German with Sketches by Fritz Kredel, 1938 (Box 58 (Cold storage), Folder 433-435)
    Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    Three copies, one hand-colored by Kredel, bound with plastic covers
  - 75. A Bibliography of the Village Press, by Melbert B. Cary Jr. (advance announcement), 1938 (Box 44, Folder 349)
  - 76. A Bibliography of the Village Press, 1903-1938, by Melbert B. Cary Jr. (announcement) (Box 44, Folder 350)
  - 77. Addenda to A Bibliography of the Village Press, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 351)
  - 78. Village Press (keepsake), 1938 (Box 45, Folder 352)
  - 79. In Memoriam; James Howell Post, 1859-1938 (Box 45, Folder 353)
  - 81. Notes on Baleana Lanigera, 1928-1938, by Melbert B. Cary Jr. (Box 45, Folder 354)
    Insert prepared for the Colophon Annual of Bookmaking, May 1938
  - 82. The Savor of the Feast; Mementos of a Dinner in Honor of Mr. and Mrs. Fritz Kredel Given by The Typophiles, October 4th, 1938. (Box 45, Folder 355)
    Includes announcement, reply card, and admission ticket.
  - 83. Progressive Layouts for "On Dry-Cow Fishing," as Designed by Bruce Rogers, by Bruce Rogers, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 356)
    Cover title: "BR Designs a Volume for the Rowfant Club"; printed for inclusion in the catalogue of the Bruce Rogers exhibition, American Institute of Graphic Arts and the Grolier Club.
  - 85. Willi's Wishful Thinking, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 357)
    Eleventh Armistice Day issue
  - 86. My Little Dachshund; A Doggerel and Madrigal by an Old Elizabethan Composer of the XXth Century; illustrated by Warren Chappell, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 358-359)
    Also one hand-colored copy containing a letter to Cary from Chappell
  - 87. The Black Art, by D. B. Updike, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 360)
    Reprint, in honor of Frederic Goudy's 74th birthday, of a pamphlet issued by Goudy in I895 and containing an essay by Updike that originally appeared in The Engraver and Printer (January 1894).
  - 88. The Oath of a Free-man. With an historical study by Lawrence C. Wroth, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 361)
  - 89. A Useful Book to Keep Things In (address book), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 362-363)
  - 90. Rules of the Library; Made in the Second Year of Richard III...November 3, 1484, 1939 (Box 52 (Oversize), Folder 364)
  - 91. Willi's Wishful Thinking (announcement and order blank), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 365)
  - 92. To the Members of the Institute (invitation to 25th anniversary meeting of the AlGA), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 366)
  - 93. The Work of Bruce Rogers; jack of All Trades, Master of One (subscription notice), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 367)
  - 95. The Club of Odd Volumes Presents an Exhibition of the Work of Bruce Rogers (announcement), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 368)
  - [95a.] American Institute of Graphic Arts, Henry Watson Kent dinner, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 369)
  - 96. Gutenberg and the Strasbourg Documents of 1439, by Otto W Fuhrmann, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 370)
  - 96. Gutenberg and the Strasbourg Documents of 1439, by Otto W Fuhrmann, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 371-373)
  - 97. The World Must Federate! Isolation versus Cooperation, by Hans Kahn, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 374)
    Twelfth Armistice Day issue
  - 98. The Missing Gutenberg Wooden Blocks, by Melbert B. Cary Jr., 1940 (Box 48, Folder 375-376)
  - 99. Gutenberg and the Strasbourg Documents of 1439 (prospectus), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 377)
  - 100. Extract from the News Letter of the American Institute of Graphic Arts (prospectus for The Missing Gutenberg Wood Blocks ), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 378)
  - 101. Songs for a Printers' Way Goose (introduction by Ruth Shepard Granniss only), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 379)
  - 103. There has just been distributed... (dues reminder card from American Institute of Graphic Arts), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 380)
  - 104. A Miscellany, comprising those books...of which copies remain... (list of Woolly Whale Press publications), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 381)
  - 105. Take Heed, America, by G. H. Archambault, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 382)
    Thirteenth Armistice Day issue
  - 106. Techniques for Dealing with Artists, by W. A. Dwiggins, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 383)
  - 107. This House of Havoc, by Carl Purington Rollins, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 384)
  - 108. A Greeting to Frederick W. Goudy from All the Typophiles, by Paul Standard, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 385)
  - 109. The Fortsas Bibliohoax, by Walter Klinefelter, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 386-387)
  - 110. An Invitation to a Kaffieklatsch, undated (Box 49, Folder 388)
  - 111. The Oldest Stencil Known (broadside), undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 389)
  - 112. Other Publications Concerning Frederic W. Goudy (card), undated (Box 49, Folder 390)
  - 113. Restauration (broadside), undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 391)
  - 114. The Press of the Woolly Whale Presents its Woolly Compliments, undated (Box 49, Folder 392)
  - 115. Presenting Some Goudy Publications, undated (Box 49, Folder 393)
  - 117. American Institute of Graphic Arts letterhead, undated (Box 49, Folder 394)
  - 118. Book Auction. April Third (notice for American Institute of Graphic Arts event), undated (Box 49, Folder 395)
  - 119. Books and Banquet = Institute Book Auction (broadside invitation for American Institute of Graphic Arts event), undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 396)
  - 120. To the Members of the American Institute of Graphic Arts (presentation slip), undated (Box 49, Folder 397)
  - 121. For the Purposes of its Forthcoming Exhibition of Private Press Books of Members (notice for American Institute of Graphic Arts event), undated (Box 49, Folder 398)
  - 122. Vote for Your Favorite Book (postcard for AIGA), undated (Box 49, Folder 399)
  - 123. You are Invited to Attend an Intimate Tasting... (broadside invitation), undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 400)
  - 124. The Oath of Hippocrates (broadside), undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 401)
  - 125. Melbert B. Cary Jr. (shipping tag), undated (Box 49, Folder 402)
  - 126. Ex Libris. Mary Flagler Cary (bookplate), undated (Box 49, Folder 403)
  - 127. From the Press of the Woolly Whale (envelope), undated (Box 49, Folder 404)
  - 128. A Prospectus issued from the Press of the Woolly Whale (envelope), undated (Box 49, Folder 405)
  - 129. Contents Book (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 406)
  - 130. From the Press of the Woolly Whale (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 407)
  - 131. To Postmaster: Contents: Book (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 408)
  - 132. Do Not Open Until Christmas (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 409)
  - 133. Contents: Book. May be opened... (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 410)
  - 134. From the Press of the Woolly Whale (shipping label), undated (Box 49, Folder 411)
  - 136. Its friends may now find The Press of the Woolly Whale ... (moving notice), undated (Box 49, Folder 412)
  - Cary family letterhead, including business cards, undated (Box 49, Folder 413)
  - Press of the Woolly Whale letterhead and mailing labels, undated (Box 49, Folder 414)
  - Melbert Cary birthday card, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 415)
  - Cary and Press of the Woolly Whale holiday cards, 1934-1940 (Box 49, Folder 416)
  - Flagler family holiday cards, undated (Box 49, Folder 417)
  - Van Vechten family holiday cards, 1937, undated (Box 49, Folder 418)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts ephemera, undated (Box 49, Folder 419)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts ephemera, 1937 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 420)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts, exhibition broadsides, undated (Box 55 (Broadside), Folder 421)
  - Continental Typefounders Association, Inc. ephemera, undated (Box 49, Folder 422)
  - Lotos Club ephemera, undated (Box 49, Folder 423)
  - National Orchestral Association ephemera, undated (Box 50, Folder 424)
  - National Orchestra Association, ephemera, undated (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 425)
  - National Orchestra Association, graduation diploma, 1930 (Box 56 (Broadside), Folder 426)
  - National Orchestral Association, So Practical a Contribution, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 427)
  - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York ephemera, undated (Box 50, Folder 428)
  - Terminal Importers ephemera, undated (Box 50, Folder 429)
  - Other ephemera, undated (Box 50, Folder 430-432)